So, what do you have in your hands?
Focus.
Minamo-giri!
Wow!
That's cool!
Minamo-giri!
So, today...
To tell you why we have these...
We're going to have a sports
chamberlain blindfolded competition!
The rules are easy.
You use your hands, do a sports
jambara, and hit someone's...
Yes.
The one who hits the person wins.
It doesn't hurt even if you hit
someone.
It doesn't hurt.
It's a non-painful thing.
I'm not going to go that far.
It's scary.
We are going to play a tournament.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Let's decide the place of the
tournament.
Let's concentrate on this.
Let's decide the winner.
I agree.
Rock-paper-scissors.
It's over.
The first one.
Pio is 6.
The next one.
1.
2.
Rock-paper-scissors.
1. 2. 3.
Bye-bye.
I'm No.3!
Konomi is No.3.
I'm No.4.
I'm going to play in the tournament.
The tournament starts!
Konomi is No.4!
I'm No.3!
I'm No.5!
Who's number one?
I'm scared!
Playing with each other?
Playing with each other.
That's scary.
Please subscribe to our channel!
This program is brought to you by six
people who are active to promote
something exciting.
Check out its various attractions to
achieve the best Myers-Brown bias
standard on the Internet, and discover
even more videos to inspire feedback and
motivation!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Please subscribe to my channel!
The first match is Junia vs Kanami.
Junia looks cool.
She looks strong.
She is cute.
Kanami, please tell us your impression.
She is very flexible.
She is a good player.
I think I'll go with the one with the
A.
Okay, Ms. Ujuri.
Yes.
I'll go with this one.
The one with the N.
What is it?
I feel like I'm not sure, but I don't
feel like I'm not sure.
Okay, let's go, everyone.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's go.
Ready.
Start.
Wow.
It's Kana Min.
Kana Min wins.
Thank you very much.
Because it was 2 minutes and 48
seconds.
2 seconds.
10 seconds.
12 seconds.
It's a quick win.
Amazing, Kanamin.
Ashi, you lost.
Kanamin is going to the semi-final.
Kanamin won.
We won the strategy.
We all decided to go from the bottom.
I see.
Thank you for watching.
Are you ready?
Yes!
I can't see anything in front of me,
but I'll shoot through Hitoka's heart.
I hate you!
I'm nervous.
Hitoka, please.
I'll be cute and cute.
I'll record with my heart.
Cute!
Hitoka is cute!
I'm perfect!
Are you ready?
Yes!
Then,
Ready? Go!
You got it!
Go!
It's a sword fight.
It's quite a rampage.
Go!
You can do it!
Did you get it?
Yes, I did.
You can still do it.
Go!
Bye bye!
I'm not sure.
Kenda! Kenda!
What was that?
My Kenda.
Let's do it again.
Can I?
Yes.
I might have hit it.
Please subscribe to this channel!
YOSHITOKA lost.
OHARU won.
I didn't know where OHARU was.
Where was OHARU?
She was sitting down.
I thought she was a loser.
I should have blamed her more.
You blamed her a lot.
OHARU won.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Next, it's a battle between Hiori and
Aki.
I don't feel anything wrong.
Hiori, what's wrong?
Can you tell us what you're feeling
today?
I think Aki is a good girl.
As expected of Sui.
I think I'll decide on this in the
novel.
I see.
I don't see anything.
You're looking at something, aren't
you?
I don't see anything.
Aki.
I'll do my best.
Come on.
Aki, you don't look uncomfortable.
I'm so excited.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Ready, go!
To be continued.
You can go forward.
Wow!
It's a good game.
It's good.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
Obviously, your hand...
Your leg?
Don't forget to subscribe our channel!
Dangerous!
It's a good match.
I'll do it.
Wow!
Akira won!
I couldn't get it open.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to make you sad.
Wow!
It's not a dinosaur.
It's a mother.
It's a mother's sacrifice.
It's a good sound.
It was a flashy sound.
It's amazing.
I was attacked.
At first, Aki was the opposite
direction.
What?
I was on the wall once.
I see.
It's a good match.
It's amazing.
I'm sad.
If you kill Hiroshi,
you'll be a police officer.
I'm sorry.
Next,
Oharu and Kanami.
They will play.
Kanami defeated Julia in 12 seconds.
What kind of match will it be?
Oharu is a good player.
She is a good player.
Let's get ready.
Please subscribe to this channel.
done
So, this is the semi-final.
It's Kanami vs Oharu.
Both of you have won once.
You two are strong.
Kanami, please tell us how you feel.
I was able to beat Julia.
I will do my best.
I'm looking forward to it.
Oharu, please tell us how you feel.
I'm a new adult.
I can't lose to an adult.
You are already 20 years old.
I'm a new adult.
I'll do my best.
It's a battle of 20s.
It's a hot battle.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's start.
Start.
Oh, gosh.
They're great.
Oh?
Their movement is fun,
like it's up to me.
Oh,öglich describing the movements
oh, no.
They're great.
Oh, thatís what youíre saying.
Please subscribe to my channel.
The winner is Oharu!
Oharu!
I won!
Oharu won!
Wow!
I want to see my move.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
But it was a great match.
I'm sorry.
I can't hear you.
Thank you.
It was great.
Oharu won.
Oharu is great.
She is a special skill.
What?
What kind of special skill?
The final match is...
Aki and Oharu.
So, it's the final round!
It's Aki and Haru.
It's a surprise combination.
Really?
I didn't expect that these two would be
the finalists.
It's going to be an interesting battle.
Haru, please cheer up.
I've come this far, so I'll do my best
to win.
Good luck!
Aki, your turn.
I'm going to do my best to win.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Let's start.
Ready, set, go!
You're calm.
It's similar to the battle before.
Like this?
No, like this.
The other way.
Wow.
Thank you for watching!
I'm tired.
Oh, no!
I'm so scared!
I'm scared!
I'm scared.
You can see the next video, too!
Subscribe to our channel!
Watch the previous video!
See you next time!
The winner of the first place is...
Chambara!
The winner of the first place is
I'm so happy.
I think everyone is surprised.
It's a premonition.
I'm so happy.
I'm the challenger.
It was fun.
I was able to feel the power of the
heart.
I don't know if it was the power of the
I wasn't concentrating on anything.
Thank you very much.
Good night.
Your turn is over.
Who are you pointing at who you like
the most in the room?
I hate lonely women who do tane go
again
I used to be a kid
Who do you think is cute?
Good
Can I see your hand again?
This hand.
Anyone here think Dami's bangs are cute
when they curl them?
Bye-bye!
Everyone! I'm Yuri adokotoba! I'm
theeltokousaiyou!
Please subscribe to our channel and
click the like button!